So sorry girls that I can't work out how to do this.
It's just it's not working at all, but never mind um So I wanted to talk to everyone
a little bit about what taboo is and how I use it you
know on cam and yeah, just Discuss a little bit about the
subjects that I cover and a little bit about the do's and don'ts and stuff like that
So I started off by just telling everyone what taboo is I
just wrote, you know taboo is a social or religious custom prohibiting or a particular
practice or forbidden association for particular place or thing So
to be for us under the umbrella of BDSM is a subject of fancy that is unspoken
illegal in practice In reality and considered forbidden So to
be you can have different meanings to different people and everyone has a different
of limits There are lots of subjects to be considered when you
are talking about taboo when someone comes in your room and says do you do taboo
that you know that would cover like a lot of subjects So
what I thought I'd do is rather than Sending listen list.
I would just do outline my top three That I
you know daily sort of speak about with clients and You
know When a guy asked you if you do taboo you can they can always say well
What does what is taboo to you? Because what taboo could be to me could be you know
can be different to someone else if that makes sense Okay
my top three Taboo and fantasy. So the first one I would say would
be consensual non-consent or CNC for sure The
real definition of this type of dom sub relationship is one of deep trust and
it's not of abuse It is a fantasy of rape play and it is quite common
But it's a kink and it's a taboo topic You know for
consensual non-consent is a mutual agreement where the dom You know
Is able to act as if the sub has wavered or consent but that completes consent is
given beforehand So if someone asks you to do this, you know You talk about it all
before you'd make sure that you've got an understanding You know You've
got complete consent beforehand and You know if this is this can
be like a permanent arrangement with someone as well Always agree your limits and
both you and the client Some guys especially I've got
a few city guys that like the thought of being forced with other men or Women for
my financial gain or pleasure Some guys might not like that.
They might want the goals. They might like to be tied up.
They might like to be used, humiliated You know by yourself and other people they
might just like to It to be like just quite normal without
you know being like that Always sort of like work out what your boundaries are for
both of you before you start a call like this to keep you both Safe and feeling comfortable
as well There's nothing worse than getting sort of halfway through a call and then
one of you feeling uncomfortable You need to you know, you put this to go like this
as well as it'd be a good experience for you and the client So
Number two, I've put incest fantasy. This is really popular with a lot of my
clients and Most clients will take a while to get into this subject and tell you
it's just a fantasy So you might have a guy come in obviously I've got taboo in
my name So I kind of expect that they might be chatting chat chat and it could take
like a good like half an hour before they Sort of think oh, yeah You build up a little
bit of a relationship in that time and then they'll come out with how they'd like
to experience sexual activity with a family member or They
might want you to pretend that you're that you are their mum a sister, auntie,
most guys always say to me oh this is just a fantasy I haven't even got a sister,
which is fine and they might also want to involve the
C&C consent, non-consent fantasy in with a family member
or talk about not giving consent to a family member and
then taking advantage. So yeah that's another one that's quite popular, I've
got some links if you want to read up about there's quite a lot of stuff, quite a
lot of stories, there's a good stuff online that you can read more and more about
to normalise it as well for you if it's something new to you.
I'd recommend reading if you're new to kind of it normalises
it for yourself as well so you talk more freely to your client.
Number three is age play. So in
my experience this is the number one requested taboo.
Age play involves treating your sub like they are a certain age, usually younger,
anywhere from toddler to teenager. As a result the sub treats their dom like
their daddy or mummy taking on the parental role of protector and caregiver and
may administer discipline and training when needed.
The sub becomes his or hers little and relies on him emotionally, physically, sexually
and sometimes financially. One of the massive things age players are
not paedophiles, the definition of paedophilia is sexual feelings towards children.
A sub is not a child, it's
a consenting adult that wants to pretend that they are a child therefore a daddy
dom who wants to be with his little girl it's those it's still an adult, little girls
in general. Some clients will like to involve siblings in this
fantasy and want to discuss ages. Personally my
response is always use your imagination, oh how old would you like me to be rather
than actually given an age, that's just a personal thing because it just feels a
bit icky sometimes if you're actually like stating an age but that's just me personally
that's how I feel. This can be a switch subject so some clients will want
to be daddy and others will want you to be mummy to them and they will want to pretend
they're a toddler or whatever. This can also go into like
nappy play and stuff like that so it can sort of go in all sorts of different directions
and when I decided to explore taboo like this I did do a lot of research first
and I did draft a lot of you know a few scripts so I sort of
got used to different role plays you know when it comes
to age. Sammy sorry, I
just said that Ellie's in the waiting room
I can't see that because I'm off the house anymore so maybe it says on your screen
that he's in the waiting room. Oh yes, I was reading
from my other screen, sorry. I just wanted to pause
there just to if anyone has any questions about the three types that I just spoke
about before I move on. Anyone? When
you're speaking about the consent non-consent and I think your laptop broke up
a little bit I wasn't so sure so can you explain a little bit more about that again
please? Okay
so I said that consent
non-consent is a dom sub relationship of trust and not abuse even
though this is a fantasy of rape play it is really common and obviously it's a taboo.
Topic. The definition for non for consensual non
-consent is a mutual agreement, where the DOM is able to act as the sub
has wavered or consent. But obviously complete consent is given beforehand, with
the understanding of this being a permanent arrangement for most people,
most circumstances, always agree limits
and boundaries first, you know, how far they
want to go with it or not go with it, or how far you want to go with it or not go
with it. Guys like to explore being tied up, used, humiliated, used
for your pleasure by other people, used for your financial gain for other people.
So yeah, just discuss all those, what, exactly what kind of like fantasy they're
looking for, before you start the call, you can discuss this
with them, you need to get it, you know, in your head exactly what they are looking
for and what your boundaries are for both of them.
Okay. So I then said,
you know, when it comes down to taboo talk, everyone is different.
And it's okay, if their hard limits are different to yours, taboo can
stem from a craving for intensity and life stress and expectations
on a person. So, you know, you need to have like, if you're if you're looking at
going into taboo, you need to have this space for that's free of, you know, judgement
and restrictions. But also was keeping yourself safe.
I've always, if someone says something that I don't want to do, or it makes me feel
uncomfortable, I just say, oh, no, sorry, I don't really offer that part of taboo.
And 99% of guys are really polite, and then they just like, oh, no problem.
And they, you know, they will go and find someone who does want to offer that.
So yeah, you have to know your own boundaries as well.
And what you how you want to guide the conversation.
And one of the things that I don't do, but obviously, you know, it's up to everyone
else what they want to do, but I just thought I'd mentioned some of the things that
make me feel uncomfortable. One of them is race play.
It's not something I've ever wanted to explore.
And I know it's a taboo fantasy, but it's, it's something I always say no to, because
it makes me feel uncomfortable. And that's fine.
And I've had guys ask, and they say, Okay, no problem.
And then they'll move on. So don't feel like you can't say no, I don't feel comfortable
with that. And if it's something that you don't want to offer.
And so the big don'ts, never write in your tag line on
AdultWork, or advertise on your profile, anything that says mummy play,
daddy play, incest, age play, do not use any of those words, because you will get
a warning. When I first started doing this, I put age play in my tagline.
And I got a warning straight away. So I profile and then I got another warning straight
away. I have on this, this, I've actually put the
link in for AdultWork's legislation and their user agreement terms of service.
So when I can actually share that with you, or you could click on that, if you wanted
to have a look through, it explains it with a lot more detail of what you should
and shouldn't be putting on your profile, and what's acceptable and what's over email.
When you're in a chat, you're a lot freer to, to, you know, to continue with the
day, but writing in emails, anything like that, or putting on your profile or tag
line, or having any photos with like, mummy play, I don't know, is the title of
it. Don't do that, because they won't, they won't allow it on the, on the website,
you will get a warning. And I think, I'm not sure how many warnings you can have,
but it's just better to not do it. And that's why I added the link in this so everyone
can have a little look through if they want to.
You can always say no. And you can always stop the call.
If someone's trying to deliberately make you feel uncomfortable after you've discussed
boundaries. It's usually because they're getting off on shocking you.
This can be quite uncomfortable. And if it's happened to me, I've just ended the
call. It's not for everyone. And it's okay to just tell the client that it's not
your preferred subject. And that isn't something that you'd like to continue with.
And most people are just absolutely fine.
Or they just leave. Maybe they feel a bit embarrassed.
But I think a lot of, not a lot, but it does sometimes happen where a guy
is trying to just shock you. You know, like you've discussed your boundaries and
he'll just go straight in with stuff that you've said isn't okay.
So just be aware of that and mindful of it.
And also just know that you can always end the call and say no.
So, okay. And
then I've just, I've added some links or ideas for your scripts.
If you're, or ideas, you know, some links for places that you could look up stories
and, you know, get some ideas if it's something that you're looking into.
Taboo works for me because it fits around my lifestyle and cam preparation.
It doesn't take me a lot of time to get ready at night.
A lot of my clients prefer it if I don't have a lot of makeup on, if I'm wearing
my pink fleece Minnie Mouse pyjamas. So this is why I kind of went into Taboo because
I've got quite good imagination. I've got quite good writing skills
and I prefer to type than to talk. So it just worked so much better for
me. And after I'd done a lot of research and read through, you know, some stories
and stuff, it kind of made me feel more comfortable around Taboo subjects.
And it just meant that at night, I can just be in my jammies in bed and type it away.
And most guys seeking Taboo do actually prefer types rather than talk, which is what
I always do because I've got the kids. Yeah, so that's how it worked for me.
And I just added some links for you all. And that was it
really. I just wanted to ask if anyone's got any questions before I thought we'd
finish up on a little bit of magic and maybe I'd draw like a tarot card for someone
just cause I know Taboo can be quite heavy, but I just wanted to know if you have
any questions. I was
wondering, like you said the top three Taboos, do
you, I know this is your main thing, so I've seen stills about it before.
But what- They're my top three. Yeah, what would you- Yeah.
How would you put it on your profile? Do you just literally write Taboo?
Obviously there's certain lines of card on there.
Yeah, so in my, it's my name, so I'm
inked Taboo mistress. And on my profile,
I've got a tab that says Taboo talk, where I sort of
write a bit more about offering Taboo. And the
way I found it is rather than putting age play, which I'm not allowed to write, I
put no limits Taboo, please email me
for request et cetera, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
I've put a link on the end of this, my profile, couldn't I?
So people take a look if they wanted to, to have a little read through of how I've
worded it and how you offer service without sort of breaking any adult
works rules. Does that make sense? Yeah. I
have a question. Can you hear me? Yeah. Okay, great.
Never used this one. Yeah, so I have
gotten a warning also about another thing.
So now I'm extra careful, but I love Taboo's topics.
So every time they're trying to me to be like a mummy or whatever, I am
just so scared that they will see in the chats or that they will scan the audio.
Like, do you know if they type and they do like, yes, mummy, you know, that also
they will be picked up by. Some screening?
No. No? No, that's, it's fine. So I read
through and just refresh my mind last night of the legislation
on AdultWork. And you know, you're putting three in.
I think it's because it says that for if you're emailing or offering it on your
profile. Does that make sense? If you're writing like incest
play in like big letters on your profile or on your tagline, it'll it'll
flag up. Yeah, I don't know they definitely.
But if you're chatting and they're like, Oh, you know, I'd like to, I'd like you
to be my mummy or my sister or whatever. That's fine.
You know, if you're chatting or talking, it's absolutely fine.
Okay, you've never had problems with that in all the time that you did it?
Yeah, no, never, never. Only if I've written it on my profile, in
a tagline or in an email, but whilst you're actually, you know, in a chat with them,
it's absolutely fine. Okay. I think it says on the
legislation like, that is fine. I can't remember how they've worded it now.
And I'll send it to you if you want. No, I've read it like quite recently.
And it said something now depicting of, I think it's the wording of anything.
If you if you upload a photo or a video, you can't depict that
it is like a pretty photo or mummy photo.
Does that make sense? Yeah. Okay. Oh, okay.
It's more, it seems more safe now to me after you.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So as long as you're chatting or
you're typing in your other live sort of chat, the sky's the limit.
Yeah. Okay, good. Kelly, was you asking
something? Yeah, I'm asking when that's okay, when someone
is like, leading towards taboo, like I haven't done it very much.
And I think this is something that I quite struggle with.
So if they're like leading towards it, and they're kind of making suggestions that
that's the kind of thing they want to talk about, but they're not big talkers, so
to speak. So they're not like, you know, a lot of them don't have very much charisma.
How do you have like a story that you go like, you always fall back on to like, get
it started? Or do you have like something that you do to kind of get the conversation
flowing? I don't have a story to lean on, because I'd be scared
that I was thinking that they were wanting a taboo chat.
And then I'd scare them a little bit if I started like, you know, completely going
into some detailed chat. What I do
say is stuff like, can
you give me an example? Like someone's like leaning, like you think that they're
leaning towards it. So if they say, for example, like, oh, so they come in, and they
want me to be a mistress, they'll address me as mistress.
And then if they'll say something like, I'm here for your pleasure, and oh, you know,
I've got no limits, you can do whatever you want to me, then I kind of know then
I get an inkling that they want to go down the, you know, non-consent route.
Or there was a guy who was really, you know, wanted that.
And then I said, oh, well, next time you come along, I'll tie you up on, I'll bend
you over chair and tie me to the chair. So you can be mounted.
Because then, yeah, the idea might, that might be something that he likes.
And then I thought, you know, you can either just dismiss that, or then you can lead
into the, you know, him saying, oh, yeah, I'd love that, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah. Does that make sense? Yeah. So would you just keep asking them questions?
Yeah, just keep asking loads of questions, because you don't want to jump the gun
and be like, oh, would you, you know, say something that might shock them a little
bit. I always get things like, oh, my God, you look loads like my stepdaughter.
And then I'm a bit like, that's a lead straight away.
Oh, do I? Yeah. I just feel a little bit like, I don't know, like,
how you then establish how far they really want you to go with that.
Um, yeah, I don't, maybe it's just having a bit of confidence to just keep asking
questions. Because I always feel like on the spot, like, oh, my God, now I need to
know what to say. And I have no idea what just This is
why it's really good to read some of them stories from Little
Roger or whatever it's called. I did add the link in but you can't see it.
Because it will literally give you a whole story about how a guy fancies his stepdaughter
and it will give you like the whole lead up, the whole like brushing past each other
and stuff like that. And it gives you loads of ideas to say, you know, like in that
instance you could say, oh, did you ever brush past her
and get a tingle when you brush past her in the kitchen or something like that.
And then that can lead on to more, you know, like, yes, no.
If you get someone who is just like, yeah, no, they can be difficult.
But if they become a regular guy, and he loves absolute filth, and
he'll literally just be like, yeah, no, and sometimes I'm a bit like, oh God, I'm
doing it wrong, but he always comes back so I think he likes it.
I just don't think he's a big ochre. Basically, I just need to man up and not
freeze on the spot and instantly end the call because I'm a bit of a pussy.
If you don't like it, and it's something that you don't want to do, then don't do
it. It doesn't bother me. I can compartmentalise.
It's just that I think, oh God, this is not me.
I don't know what I'm doing. And then I just end the call because I think, oh, they're
expecting me to know what to say next. And I never know what to say next.
And I'm like, oh, that's nice. Have a little read into it and then go from there
and tell you how you feel about it. When we're rolling around in bed one time, I'll
give you a little lesson. I'm usually the backdrop in your taboo stories.
Is there anyone else who's got a question?
I just want to look. Has anyone typed anything?
I can't see because I'm now on my phone, even more useless.
Yeah, I'll type some stuff. She said, I think you really have to draw it out of
some clients. Like, draw it out what their fantasy or taboo is.
Assure them it's a safe space, no judgement, etc.
Ask what their porn category of choice is.
Oh yeah, that's brilliant. I always say that.
If they say, oh, I'm really horny, I'll be like, oh, are you watching porn?
And they'll either say yes or no. What porn do you like?
And that's a great way of finding out what they like or don't like.
Yeah, exactly. And she also said, I ask what their darkest fantasies are or she tells
them hers first. So that way it might be, might give them like, you know, if you
tell yours first, then they're probably more likely to open up a little bit more
to you, aren't they? Even if yours is made up or whatever else.
That's always a good one, like a good backstory to have actually, thinking about
what Kelly just said, is have a little sort of, you know, your darkest fantasy, like
a sort of script in your head of what yours is, so you can always give that to them
first. And if you make it more like it's insinuating rather
than full out, it can then lead to more questions and then they'll ask more details
about it. And then you can sort of, you know, go from there.
If you have like a little sort of fantasy about, I don't know, I
normally say my step brother. So I'll say like, oh, you know, he's really hot,
he used to live together and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then you can lead on from there. I've literally written down on my notebook,
stop being pussy, ask more questions. Just pretend you had
like a really hot stepbrother growing up.
And then like, I'm not going to get right from there or a
really young stepdad who is really hot. Yeah.
And yeah, like, we're also just keeping it a safe space and not being judgmental.
And, you know, if they ask something that you don't feel comfortable with in the
flight, so you can just say, oh, no, I don't really, I don't really know a lot about
that. And then it's fine. And like I said, guys will try and shock you.
So just be aware of that as well. That's another sort of like kink and fetish to
really try and shock you and see if your facial expression...
And changes and stuff like that.